export const alphabets = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "A a",
    front: "ALLIGATOR",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/alligator.svg").default,
    back: "APPLE",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/apple.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "B b",
    front: "BAT",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/bat.svg").default,
    back: "BASKETBALL",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/basketball.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "C c",
    front: "COW",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/cow.svg").default,
    back: "CAR",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/car.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: "D d",
    front: "DOG",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/dog.svg").default,
    back: "DOCTOR",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/doctor.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    title: "E e",
    front: "ELEPHANT",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/elephant.svg").default,
    back: "EGG",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/egg.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    title: "F f",
    front: "FROG",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/frog.svg").default,
    back: "FAN",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/fan.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    title: "G g",
    front: "GIRAFFE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/giraffe.svg").default,
    back: "GUITAR",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/guitar.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    title: "H h",
    front: "HORSE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/horse.svg").default,
    back: "HAT",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/hat.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    title: "I i",
    front: "IGUANA",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/iguana.svg").default,
    back: "ICE CREAM",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/ice-cream.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    title: "J j",
    front: "JELLYFISH",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/jellyfish.svg").default,
    back: "JACKET",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/jacket.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    title: "K k",
    front: "KANGAROO",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/kangaroo.svg").default,
    back: "KEY",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/key.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    title: "L l",
    front: "LION",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/lion.svg").default,
    back: "LIGHT",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/light.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    title: "M m",
    front: "MONKEY",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/monkey-1.svg").default,
    back: "MONEY",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/money.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    title: "N n",
    front: "NIGHTINGALE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/nightingale.svg").default,
    back: "NECKLACE",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/necklace.svg").default,
  },

  {
    id: 15,
    title: "O o",
    front: "OWL",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/owl.svg").default,
    back: "ORANGE",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/orange.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    title: "P p",
    front: "PIG",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/pig.svg").default,
    back: "PEN & PAPER",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/pen-and-paper.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    title: "Q",
    lowercase: "q",
    front: "QUAIL",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/quail.svg").default,
    back: "QUEEN",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/queen.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    title: "R r",
    front: "RHINO",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/rhino.svg").default,
    back: "ROBOT",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/robot.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    title: "S s",
    front: "SHEEP",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/sheep.svg").default,
    back: "SHIRT",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/shirt.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    title: "T t",
    front: "TIGER",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/tiger.svg").default,
    back: "TRAIN",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/train.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    title: "U u",
    front: "UNICORN",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/unicorn.svg").default,
    back: "UMBRELLA",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/umbrella.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    title: "V v",
    front: "VULTURE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/vulture.svg").default,
    back: "VACUUM",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/vacuum.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    title: "W w",
    front: "WHALE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/whale.svg").default,
    back: "WAGON",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/wagon.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    title: "X x",
    front: "X-RAY FISH",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/x-ray-fish.svg").default,
    back: "XYLOPHONE",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/xylophone.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    title: "Y y",
    front: "YAK",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/yak.svg").default,
    back: "YARN",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/yarn.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    title: "Z z",
    front: "ZEBRA",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/animals/zebra.svg").default,
    back: "ZIPPER",
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/other/zipper.svg").default,
  },
];

export const numbers = [
  {
    id: 0,
    title: 0,
    front: "ZERO",
    back: "ZERO",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-0.svg").default],
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "I",
    front: "ONE",
    back: "ONE",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-1.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "II",
    front: "TWO",
    back: "TWO",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-2.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-2.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "III",
    front: "THREE",
    back: "THREE",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-3.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-3.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: "IV",
    front: "FOUR",
    back: "FOUR",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-4.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-4.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    title: "V",
    front: "FIVE",
    back: "FIVE",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-5.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-5.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    title: "VI",
    front: "SIX",
    back: "SIX",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-6.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-6.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    title: "VII",
    front: "SEVEN",
    back: "SEVEN",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-7.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-7.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    title: "VIII",
    front: "EIGHT",
    back: "EIGHT",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-8.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-8.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    title: "IX",
    front: "NINE",
    back: "NINE",
    frontIcon: [require("../assets/icons/robots/number-9.svg").default],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-9.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    title: "X",
    front: "TEN",
    back: "TEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-0.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-10.svg").default,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    title: "XI",
    front: "ELEVEN",
    back: "ELEVEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-11.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 12,
    title: "XII",
    front: "TWELVE",
    back: "TWELVE",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-2.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-12.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 13,
    title: "XIII",
    front: "THIRTEEN",
    back: "THIRTEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-3.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-13.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 14,
    title: "XIV",
    front: "FOURTEEN",
    back: "FOURTEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-4.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-14.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 15,
    title: "XV",
    front: "FIFTEEN",
    back: "FIFTEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-5.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-15.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 16,
    title: "XVI",
    front: "SIXTEEN",
    back: "SIXTEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-6.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-16.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 17,
    title: "XVII",
    front: "SEVENTEEN",
    back: "SEVENTEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-7.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-17.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 18,
    title: "XVIII",
    front: "EIGHTEEN",
    back: "EIGHTEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-8.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-18.svg").default,

  },

  {
    id: 19,
    title: "XIX",
    front: "NINETEEN",
    back: "NINETEEN",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-1.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-9.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-19.svg").default,

  },
  {
    id: 20,
    title: "XX",
    front: "TWENTY",
    back: "TWENTY",
    frontIcon: [
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-2.svg").default,
      require("../assets/icons/robots/number-0.svg").default,
    ],
    backIcon: require("../assets/icons/robots/robot-20.svg").default,
  },
];

export const shapes = [
  {
    id: 0,
    title: "",
    front: "SQUARE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/square.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "",
    front: "TRIANGLE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/triangle.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "",
    front: "HEART",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/heart.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "",
    front: "STAR",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/star.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: "",
    front: "CIRCLE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/circle.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    title: "",
    front: "HEXAGON",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/hexagon.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    title: "",
    front: "PENTAGON",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/pentagon.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    title: "",
    front: "RECTANGLE",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/rectangle.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    title: "",
    front: "OVAL",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/oval.svg").default
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    title: "",
    front: "DIAMOND / RHOMBUS",
    frontIcon: require("../assets/icons/ocean/diamond.svg").default
  }
]


export const lessons = [
  {
    lesson: "ABCs",
    categories: ["animals", "other"],
  },
];
